What we need to do in business,
brand development, everything,
is appreciate that
you are here, they are here.
It's not about reaching
them.
It's about not being where you started.
Because even if you went,
how fast does Usain Bolt run 100 meters?
Let's say he's nine seconds
and you're 12 seconds,
the fact you will never get to
nine is fine, because if you get to 11,
you're going to feel fucking good about
yourself. If you get to 10,
you're going to feel fucking ecstatic.
Even if you start at, I don't know,
my 100-meter time, 18 seconds, getting to
15 is a damn good accomplishment.
And do you know what?
It's not even the achievements
that feel good, it's making progress.
It's not even being super wealthy
that feels good, it's about the progress.
It's not even getting promoted at jujitsu
that feels good, it's about the progress